Finding Aid for the Eiko Ishioka papers LSC.2288
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Fashion and uniforms, circa 1971-2008
  - Subseries 5.1: Issey Miyake, circa 1971-1980
    - Clipping: Esquire magazine "Issey Miyake by Eiko Ishioka with David Byrne", undated (Box 519, Folder 4)
    - Publicity, circa 1978, undated (Box 700, Folder 3, Box 517)
    - Fashion show ad (not Ishioka design), 1979 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 5.2: Houston Rockets, 2002-2003
    Consists of material relating to Ishioka's designs of Houston Rockets uniforms and logo, including several drafts of presentation books containing computer drawings. Uniforms include full sets of jerseys and shorts, and warm-up jackets and pants. Accessories include baseball caps and towels.
    - Sketches and notes, 2002-2003 (Box 155, Folder 1-3, Box 154, Folder 7)
      Includes some correspondence and printed-out computer drawings.
    - Uniform sketches, circa 2002 (Box 168, Folder 4-5)
    - Uniform and logo computer drawings, circa 2002-2003 (Box 168, Folder 6-7)
    - Uniform photographs, 2004-2005 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Presentation books, 2002-2003 (Box 175, Box 176, Box 177)
    - Uniforms, circa 2003 (Box 189, Box 190, Box 191)
    - Accessories, circa 2003 (Box 188)
    - Clippings and ephemera, 2003-2009 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 5.3: Winter Olympics, Salt Lake City, 2002
    Material relates to uniforms created by Ishioka for selected members of the Swiss, Canadian, Japanese and Spanish teams, and contains photographs, slides, and transparencies of uniforms, uniform development, events, and athletes.
    - Uniform images (binders), 2001-2002 (Box 148, Folder 7-10)
    - Uniform images: slides, circa 2002 (Box 461, Folder 5)
    - Publicity and clippings, 2002 (Box 704, Box 516, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 5.4: Summer Olympics, Beijing, 2008
    Publicity relating to Ishioka's work as director of costume design for the opening ceremony.
    - Publicity and clippings, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 9-10, Box 516, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 5.5: Commes des Garçons: catalog, 1980 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    Includes images of Ishioka as model.
- Series 6: Book design, 1971-2001
  This series contains material relating to Ishioka's book design work, especially the two volumes dedicated to her own career Eiko by Eiko (1983) and Eiko on Stage (2000). It also includes items related to several other books Ishioka art directed, some of which were Parco publications.
  Material documenting her work for Kadokawa Books is located in Series 9. Kadokawa paperbacks are in Series 15 (boxes 668-669).
  - Subseries 6.1: Eiko by Eiko, 1982-1983
    Includes a variety of material that documents production stages of Eiko by Eiko, the 1983 publication detailing Ishioka's career to that point. Material includes drawings, page dummies and layouts, and typeface examples. Also present are a number of images of Ishioka, Nicholas Callaway, and others at work on the book's design as well as images of the final product and Tokyo launch party. See Series 11 for related audiovisual material.
    A number of color transparencies in this collection depicting various material from Ishioka's career appear to have been used for production work for Eiko by Eiko, or for a later unrealized book project. These are located under series and subjects depicted, or under Series 12: Career, Subseries 12.2: Portfolios.
    - Production material, circa 1982-1983 (Box 171, Box 184, Folder 3-7, Box 187, Folder 4-6, Box 211)
      Production material includes page layout drawings and sketches, page dummies, book jacket drawings (box 171), typeface samples and layouts, title layouts for English and Japanese versions, some copy, and notes.
    - Film strips, circa 1982-1983 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      Negatives, contact sheets, and prints of film strips that appear in the book.
    - Book jacket proof, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Production work: photographs, 1983, circa 1983 (Box 148, Folder 12, Box 715, Folder 2)
    - Production work: contact sheets, circa 1983 (Box 148, Folder 13-14, Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Production work: slides, 1982 (Box 501)
    - Book images (final product): photographs, slides, transparencies, circa 1983 (Box 464, Box 465)
    - Launch party, Tokyo: photographs, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
    - Publicity and Callaway catalog, 1983-1984 (Box 517, Folder 5)
    - Poster (ad for book), 1983 (Box 6)
  - Subseries 6.2: Eiko on Stage, 2000
    Subseries contains a small amount of material related to the publication of Eiko on Stage, which details a number of Ishioka's stage, film, and multimedia projects.
    - Photographs (copies, thumbnails), circa 2000 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Book tour (bulk): photographs, circa 2000 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Event invitations (Japan Society, New York), undated (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Book jacket proof, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Book jackets, 2000 (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Callaway catalog, 2000 (Box 520, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 6.3: Record of Kyoto, 1973-circa 1974
    Biography/History
    Art direction of five-volume photographic book.
    - Photographs, 1973, circa 1974 (Box 149, Folder 7, Box 150, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries 6.4: The Day We Changed the Channel to Watch Commercials: The Age of Toshi Sugiyama, 1978
    - Photographs, circa 1978 (Box 157, Folder 6-7)
    - Related exhibition photographs, circa 1978 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Slides, transparencies, photographs, 1978 (Box 465)
    - Commercial storyboards and scripts (Shiseido and others) (copies), circa 1960s (Box 195)
  - Subseries 6.5: Tamara de Lempicka: The Myth of the Portrait, 1980
    Material also includes photographs of Ishioka's visit to de Lempicka in Cuernavaca, Mexico in 1979.
    - Book, Mexico visit: photographs, contact sheets, circa 1979 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Mexico visit: photographs (snapshots), 1979 (Box 150, Folder 4, Box 715, Folder 3-4)
    - Slides, transparencies, photographs, 1980 (Box 465)
    - Posters, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Promo booklet, circa 1980 (Box 700, Folder 4)
    - Book (Box 543, Box 736)
  - Subseries 6.6: Tariki: Embracing Despair, Discovering Peace (Hiroyuki Itsuki), 2001
    - Itsuki portrait, book cover: photographs, circa 2001 (Box 150, Folder 5-7, Box 157, Folder 5)
      Includes contact sheets, negatives.
    - Poster, circa 2001 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 2001 (Box 704)
  - Subseries 6.7: Other publications, 1971-1978
    Contains posters and related material for books designed by Ishioka; also a concert program.
    - ELVIS.: poster, circa 1971 (Box 7)
    - The Human Century, A Seven-Volume Collection of Contemporary Essays: posters, 1973 (Box 10)
    - The Human Century, A Seven-Volume Collection of Contemporary Essays: poster production material (Box 43)
    - The Human Century, A Seven-Volume Collection of Contemporary Essays (and others?): sphere image computer drawing (printed-out) (Box 288)
    - Live Under the Sky '78: concert program, 1978 (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified cover design, undated (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 6.8: Book design binders, 1970s-1983 (Box 464, Box 465)
    Include slides and transparencies depicting numerous book and jacket designs including Eiko by Eiko, Tamara de Lempicka: The Myth of the Portrait, Spectral Women, The Day We Changed the Channel to Watch Commercials, various Kadokawa publications, and Japanese textbooks.
- Series 7: Periodical design, circa 1970-1991
  This series contains material related to art direction and design work for Wild Times magazine and other journals, as well as for individual magazine articles or series. Items include production drawings, layouts, and photographs; and photographs, slides, transparencies, and snapshots taken on location shoots. Drafts of magazine writings and copies of published articles by Ishioka are in Series 12, Subseries 12.3 Writings.
  - Subseries 7.1: Wild Times (Yasei jidai), 1974-1978
    Production material for literary magazine Wild Times, published by Kadokawashoten (Kadokawa Books); Ishioka was art director from 1974 to 1978. Material includes photographs, drawings, and page layouts. Mounted covers are mounted on foam core; mounted pages are on cardboard.
    - Production material, circa 1974-1978 (Box 150, Folder 8-10, Box 151, Folder 1-3, Box 160, Folder 5-8)
      Many photographs are marked up for production.
    - Photographs, slides, transparencies (binders), circa 1974-1978 (Box 470)
    - Covers, circa 1974-1978 (Box 473)
    - Mounted covers, circa 1974-1978 (Box 471, Box 472)
    - Mounted pages, circa 1974-1978 (Box 474, Box 475, Box 476, Box 477, Box 478, Box 479, Box 480, Box 481)
    - Poster of cover (alien sitting on bench), undated (Box 37)
    - Publications, 1974-1978 (Box 690, Box 691, Box 692, Box 693, Box 694, Box 695, Box 696, Box 697, Box 698, Box 699)
    - Duplicate publications: Wild Times (Box 731, Box 732, Box 733, Box 734)
  - Subseries 7.2: "Autumn in Sofia", 1975-1976
    Images in this subseries were taken in Bulgaria and are most likely related to a project Ishioka was involved with creating magazine photo serializations of Hiroyuki Itsuki novels. In 1976, she traveled to Bulgaria with photographer Hajime Sawatari to work on the first series "Autumn in Sofia."
    - Slides and transparencies, 1975-1976 (Box 455, Box 456, Folder 1-3)
    - Photographs, circa 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 7.3: "The Dark Barge", 1977
    Material relates to a photo serialization written by Hiroyuki Itsuki; Ishioka served art director, Kazumi Kurigami, photographer. Shot on location in Lisbon and published in Non-no magazine.
    - Slides, transparencies, photographs, 1977 (Box 444)
    - Photographs (snapshots), 1977 (Box 204, Folder 1-2)
    - Publications: Non-no magazines, 1976-1977 (Box 512, Box 513)
  - Subseries 7.4: "Go Go and Go Go Go", circa 1978
    Material relates to an article for Fashion News magazine; Ishioka served as art director, costume/set designer.
    - Slides, transparencies, photographs, circa 1978 (Box 449)
  - Subseries 7.5: "On the Island Was a Breeze: Issey Miyake in New Caledonia", 1979
    Images relate to Issey Miyake fashion feature for More magazine; Ishioka served as art/creative director.
    - Photographs (snapshots), circa 1979 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1979 (Box 393, Box 441, Box 442, Box 443, Box 444)
      Some may relate to "The First Supper" (Subseries 7.6).
  - Subseries 7.6: "The First Supper: Issey Miyake in the New Hebrides", 1980
    Contains material relating to Issey Miyake fashion feature for Fashion News magazine; Ishioka served as art/creative director. Snapshots were most likely taken while on location for this project.
    - Photographs (snapshots), circa 1980 (Box 151, Folder 5-6, Box 715, Folder 6)
    - Slides, 1980 (Box 436)
      Also includes some images of Issey Miyake Show poster/ad.
    - Publication: Fashion News (no 194), 1980 (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 7.7: Native American project, circa 1984-1985
    Material relates to an unrealized magazine project.
    - Slides, circa 1984-1985 (Box 460, Box 461, Folder 1-3)
    - Will Sampson: slides and photographs, circa 1984-1985 (Box 461, Folder 2)
    - Contact sheets and negatives (binders), circa 1984 (Box 713)
  - Subseries 7.8: Other publications, circa 1970-1991
    - Other magazines/serials, circa 1970-1978 (Box 349, Folder 5-7, Box 351, Folder 7-8, Box 352, Folder 9, Box 482)
      Production material including drawings, layouts, and dummies for other Japanese periodicals such as Language Life and Feature Chatting (or Feature Story). Box 482 contains binders of slides, transparencies, and photographs for publications that may be magazines, including those with labels "Urban Housing" and "Design." Some material may relate to textbook series.
    - JAAA reports (Japanese Advertising Agencies Association), 1972 (Box 518, Folder 5)
      Cover design by Ishioka.
    - UCLA Extension summer catalog cover, 1991 (Box 700, Folder 7)
      Cover designed by Ishioka. Includes one full catalog, two covers; all signed.
    - Various proofs: unidentified publications, undated (Box 60)
    - Duplicate publications: other journals (Box 734, Box 735)
- Series 8: Record cover design, circa 1970-2006
  Primarily production material relating to record covers designed by Ishioka, especially the Miles Davis album Tutu (1986). Material for various projects includes photographs, layouts, drawings and sketches, proofs, posters, slides and transparencies, and record covers.
  - Subseries 8.1: Tutu (Miles Davis), 1986
    Material relating to Grammy award winning record cover designed by Ishioka with photographs by Irving Penn. See Series 12, Subseries 12.2 for images of Ishioka with Davis at various events.
    - Photographs (Irving Penn), circa 1986, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 8)
      Five Irving Penn photographic prints (20x24): two of Davis' hands, two front cover image, one back cover image. Folder also contains one photo of Davis taken by S. Ishikawa, 1991 (16x20), which does not appear to be related to Tutu.
    - Photographs (marked up for production), circa 1986 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and invoice, 1986 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Draft and notes (Japanese), circa 1986 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Production material, circa 1986 (Box 172, Folder 8-13, Box 183, Folder 9-11)
      Includes layouts, dummies, drawings, type samples, copy, graphics, sketches, and notes.
    - Sticker samples, circa 1986 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Record covers (final product), 1986 (Box 178)
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1986 (Box 462)
    - Publicity, 2006 (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 8.2: Miles Davis Story, circa 1971
    - Photographs of cover, undated (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1971, undated (Box 462)
  - Subseries 8.3: Bibari (Bibari Maeda), 1976
    Slides are of record cover and promotional images.
    - Slides, 1976 (Box 457)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Poster, circa 1976 (Box 2)
  - Subseries 8.4: Five Stars (V.S.O.P. Quintet), 1979
    - Proofs and drawings, circa 1979 (Box 109, Box 350, Folder 1)
    - Record cover, 1979 (Box 178)
  - Subseries 8.5: Other projects, circa 1975-circa 1985
    - The 5th Dimension: poster production material, undated (Box 39)
    - 111 Sullivan Street (Yoshiaki Masuo): photographs and contact sheets, circa 1975 (Box 151, Folder 10, Box 160, Folder 3-4)
    - Mirror of My Mind (Ryo Kawasaki): production material, circa 1979 (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - Night? (Tony WIlliams): cover image, undated (Box 185, Folder 7, Box 349, Folder 2)
    - A Touch of Love (Kimiko Itoh): dummies and proofs, circa 1985 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Unplugged (Rolling Stones): drawings and notes (unrealized project?), undated (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Unknown record (probably Osamu Kitayama): photographs, undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Nonesuch Records material, undated (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 8.6: Various covers: slides, transparencies, photographs, negatives, 1970s-1980s (Box 429, Box 462, Box 463)
    Bulk is binders with images of covers including Five Stars (V.S.O.P.), A Touch of Love (Kimiko Itoh) and others; also includes images of album graphics.
  - Subseries 8.7: Record covers (final products), 1970s (Box 178, Box 179, Box 180, Box 181)
    Many are record covers only, with no discs. Albums include jazz, classical, and collections.
- Series 9: Advertising, 1962-2005
  This series contains material related to Ishioka's advertising work for commercial clients Parco, Kadokawa Books, Sanyo Fashion House, Shiseido, Tokyu, Diana, Nike, and others. Material includes posters, photographs, slides, transparencies, negatives, drawings, poster proofs, and some print ads. Some of the well-known personalities featured in various campaigns include Faye Dunaway, Dominique Sanda, Aurore Clement, Kenji Sawada, Annie Leibovitz, Lisa Lyon, Rene Russo, Toshiro Mifune, Grace Jones, and Kimiko Kasai. Ishioka's ongoing work with Parco is well-documented with hundreds of posters, photographs, and slides, and some location snapshots.
  See also Series 11 for audiovisual material relating to television commercials for Parco, Kadokawa Books, Sanyo, Shiseido, Nike, and others.
  Series is arranged alphabetically by client. Material for the numerous Parco advertising campaigns has been arranged into four subseries: 9.11 Faye Dunaway campaigns (including Can West Wear East?), 9.12 India/Morocco/Kenya campaigns, 9.13 Kenji Sawada campaigns, and 9.14 Other campaigns.
  Oversize posters in boxes 285-320 are housed onsite at YRL.
  Related Material
  Detailed information about many of these campaigns can be found in Eiko by Eiko.
  - Subseries 9.1: Apple computer (brochure), 1988
    - Transparencies (binder), 1988 (Box 427)
  - Subseries 9.2: Diana, 1974-1978
    - Slides and transparencies, 1975-1977, undated (Box 404, Box 405, Box 406, Box 407, Box 408, Box 427, Box 429, Box 430, Folder 1-2)
    - Hot Hot Sandal.: poster, undated (Box 5)
    - Mike! Don't Touch the Shoes!: poster, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Sandal Invited. Summer Got Burnt.: poster, undated (Box 5)
    - Sandal Won in Brown Summer.: poster, undated (Box 5)
    - She Experienced Wearing High Heels: poster, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Shoes Occasionally Make a Woman Bold: poster, undated (Box 5)
    - "Wait Until I Take My Boots Off:" poster, undated (Box 5)
    - You, Wear Pink Sandals: poster, undated (Box 5)
    - Poster proofs and drawings, 1970s (Box 41)
      Includes proofs for poster Lauren, You Were Red Shoes That Night.
  - Subseries 9.3: Epoca, 1996
    Material relates to four different poster images for the Epoca campaign. Photographs include production material and copies of ads (box 174). Slides and transparencies include images of posters on public display. See Series 11 for Epoca audiovisual material.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 152, Folder 1, Box 174, Folder 5-6, Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Contact sheets, undated (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 708)
    - Snapshots of photo shoot, undated (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Slides and transparencies, 1996 (Box 428)
    - Epoca is Yours: posters, circa 1996 (Box 7)
  - Subseries 9.4: Erco, undated
    - Transparencies, undated (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - Erco We Make Light Work: poster, undated (Box 8)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 42)
  - Subseries 9.5: Hitachi, circa 1977
    Some slides of Kimiko may not document Hitachi campaign. See Series 11 for audiovisual material.
    - Kimiko: slides, 1977 (Box 458, Box 425)
    - Poster, circa 1977 (Box 9)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 43)
  - Subseries 9.6: Kadokawa Books, 1972-1977
    Primarily contains posters advertising Kadokawa Books (Kadokawashoten). Photographs, slides, and transparencies may also relate to book design work. See Series 11 for audiovisual material.
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1977 (Box 152, Folder 4-7, Box 194, Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Snapshots of photo shoots, circa 1974-1977 (Box 152, Folder 8, Box 715, Folder 25)
    - Contact sheets, circa 1974-1977 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Slides and transparencies, 1972-1977 (Box 393, Box 394, Box 395, Box 396, Box 397, Box 398, Box 399, Box 400, Box 401, Box 402, Box 403, Box 404, Box 405, Box 434, Box 435)
    - Alone. Read Light. Open Wind.: poster, undated (Box 11)
    - Alone. Read Today. Open Tomorrow.: poster, undated (Box 11)
    - Book Girls Have Already Become A Negative Symbol.: poster, 1977 (Box 12)
    - The Book That Travels: poster, 1974 (Box 12)
    - The Book That Turns into Sand: poster, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Don't Want to Be a Boring Adult: poster (version one: rain, cars), 1977 (Box 11)
    - Don't Want to Be a Boring Adult: poster (version two: sitting on porch, two sizes), 1977 (Box 12)
    - Having Books to Read Til They Get Worn Out.: poster, undated (Box 12)
    - Having Trips Just for Reading Books: poster, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Hey, Hot Man! This Is a Hot Book! Hi, Hit Woman! This Is a Hit Book!: poster (1 of 2 parts), 1977 (Box 11)
    - Page Rang. A Woman Was in the Wind.: poster, undated (Box 12)
    - San Francisco Book Fair: poster (oversize horizontal), undated (Box 311)
    - Want to Hold. This Day. This Book.: poster, undated (Box 12)
    - Women! Turn Off Your TV! Women! Close Your Magazines!: poster, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Smaller posters, 1970s-1980s (Box 12)
  - Subseries 9.7: Kanebo: An Deux Mille, Lady 80, 1979
    See Series 11 for audiovisual material.
    - Slides and transparencies, 1979, undated (Box 419, Box 420, Box 421, Box 422, Box 423, Box 427)
  - Subseries 9.8: Kissa, 1977
    Slides and transparencies also have some logotype images. Kissa logotype photographs are located in Series 10.
    - Slides and transparencies, 1977 (Box 428)
    - Layouts, undated (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Kissa: posters, circa 1977 (Box 38)
    - Kissa Sport: posters, 1977 (Box 38)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 45, Box 46)
  - Subseries 9.9: Nike, 2005
    Material relates to Ishioka's mask designs for Nike television ad campaign, directed by Tarsem (Singh). See also Series 11 for audiovisual material.
    - Drawings, circa 2005 (Box 169, Folder 1-2)
    - Drawings (copies), undated (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Photographs (copies), 2005 (Box 152, Folder 10-11)
    - Clippings, 2005 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 9.10: Nissan, circa 1971
    See also Series 11 for audiovisual material.
    - Transparencies and photographs (binder), circa 1971 (Box 507)
  - Subseries 9.11: Parco: Faye Dunaway campaigns, circa 1979
    Material related to several Parco campaigns featuring Faye Dunaway, especially Can West Wear East?. Snapshots are of ad shoots. Posters in box 304 are oversized, horizontal; posters in box 17 include two signed by Dunaway. See also Series 11 for film and other audiovisual material relating to Parco television commercials.
    - Photographs, circa 1979 (Box 162, Folder 1, Box 193)
    - Photographs (snapshots), 1979, circa 1979 (Box 162, Folder 2, Box 715, Folder 15-17)
    - Contact sheets, circa 1979 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Slides, circa 1979 (Box 353, Box 354, Box 355, Box 356)
    - Can West Wear East?: color transparencies, circa 1979 (Box 355)
    - Can West Wear East?: poster, 1979 (Box 304, Box 17)
    - Can West Wear East?: poster production material (Box 309)
    - Faye Dunaway: poster, circa 1979 (Box 304)
    - This Is the Poster for Parco: poster (two versions), 1979 (Box 304, Box 17)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 52)
  - Subseries 9.12: Parco: India, Morocco, Kenya campaigns, 1977-1978
    Material relates to a three-part, year-long campaign focusing on women in remote areas of the selected countries. See also Series 11 for film and other audiovisual material relating to Parco television commercials.
    - Photographs (snapshots): India and Morocco, circa 1977 (Box 162, Folder 4-5, Box 715, Folder 18-20)
    - Photographs (snapshots): Kenya (possibly), 1978 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Slides and transparencies, 1977-1978 (Box 356, Box 357, Box 358, Folder 1-3, Box 359, Box 360, Box 361, Box 362, Box 363, Box 364, Box 365)
    - Ah, Our Roots! (India): poster, 1977 (Box 21)
    - I Have Come Thousands of Miles in Search of You, Vision of Spectral Wonders (Morocco): poster, 1977 (Box 303)
    - My Dear Superstar (Kenya): poster, 1978 (Box 21)
    - My Dear Superwoman (Kenya): poster, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Spectral Women (book) (Box 543)
  - Subseries 9.13: Parco: Kenji Sawada campaigns, 1979-1980
    Snapshots and some other images were taken on location in the Philippines. See also Series 11 for film and other audiovisual material relating to Parco television commercials.
    - Photographs, circa 1979 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Photographs (snapshots), 1979, circa 1979 (Box 162, Folder 6-7, Box 715, Folder 21-22)